http://gregpak.com/privacy-policy/

Princess Who Saved Herself | Ronin Island | Darth Vader | Hulk | Please consider donating to writer Bill Mantlo's ongoing care!
Privacy Policy
Who we are
Our website address is: http://gregpak.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
We do not currently have comments enabled. But if comments ever were enabled, these policies would apply:
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
We do not currently make it possible for users to upload media to the website. But if that functionality ever were enabled, this would apply:
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Newsletter
We currently use the MailPoet WordPress plugin to maintain an email newsletter. We use MailPoet’s automated signup confirmation (double opt-in system) to ensure that subscribers have opted in to receiving the newsletter.
To deliver this email newsletter and help us gauge the functionality, reach, and effectiveness of our communications, we collect the following information from users:
Email address;
Names;
IP address;
Newsletter: opens, clicks, opt-ins;
Cookies
We do not currently enable comments or account creation. But if we were to enable those services, these cookie policies would apply:
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Who we share your data with
We do not share your data with any third parties, unless in response to a legal request (like a search warrant, court order or subpoena) or in reporting a suspected crime to the authorities.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Contact information
newsletter at gregpak dot com
Search for:
Subscribe to Blog via Email
Enter your email address to subscribe to this blog and receive notifications of new posts by email.
Email Address
Subscribe
Calendar
2020.12.04 – VoteRiders event – Text Georgia voters and talk about quarantine comfort food!2020.11.11 – DARTH VADER #7 in stores this Wednesday!2020.10.25 – Greg’s on the Baltimore Comic Con’s STAR WARS comics panel!
Categories
Books Written by Greg Pak
ABC Disgusting
Kickstarter Secrets
Make Comics Like the Pros
Planet Hulk (prose novel)
Sign up for the Greg Pak Newsletter!
Subscribe to the Greg Pak Comic Shop Newsletter
Thank you for signing up for the Greg Pak Newsletter!
Proudly powered by WordPress
© 1999-2020 Pak Man Productions. All rights reserved.
